escort-ireland.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Statement - Irish Escort Website Privacy Policy - Escort Ireland

**“The Website” – www.escort-ireland.com  
“The Service Provider” –    
“You” - the User of the Website**

This privacy statement explains the data collection and use practices of The Website.

### Anonymous Access

You can visit The Website without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself.

### Personal Information Collection

The Service Provider endeavours to collect your personal information only with your knowledge and consent. The type of personal information we may collect could include, for example, your name, email address or telephone number, and situations where we may collect personal information could include, and for example, when you register to use specific website services provided by The Service Provider or when contacting The Service Provider contact us. If you choose to provide The Service Provider with personal information it will be used in support of the intended purposes stated at the time at which it was collected and subject to any preferences indicated by you.

### Non-Personally Identifying Information

The Service Provider may also collect non-personally identifying information about your visit to The Website, like your IP address and details of your browsing activities within The Website.

### How Will The Service Provider Use Your Information?

The Service Provider may use your information for a number of purposes which could include providing website services to you, responding to your enquiries and helping us manage and develop our website.

### When Will The Service Provider Disclose Your Information To Others?

The Service Provider will not pass your personal information to any third parties unless you give us express permission to do so or we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on The Service Provider; (b) protect and defend The Service Providers rights or property; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the safety of anyone.

### Cookies

The Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer if you agree. These cookies allow The Service Provider to distinguish you from other users of the website which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse The Website and also allows us to improve The Website.

#### Session cookies

Session cookies allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They may be used for a variety of purposes such as remembering what a user has put in their shopping basket as they browse around a site. They could also be used for security when a user is accessing internet banking or to facilitate use of webmail. These session cookies expire after a browser session so would not be stored longer term. For this reason session cookies may sometimes be considered less privacy intrusive than persistent cookies.

Name| Typical Content| Usage  
---|---|---  
PHPSESSID| Random string| Session ID  
ei_sessionhash| Random string| Message Boards session ID  
ei_thread_lastview| String| Message Boards - Last Viewed Threads  
skimlinks_enabled| Value 1| Message Boards - Thread preferences  
ei_forum_view| String| Message Boards - Forum View preferences  
_utmc| Random number| Google Analytics  
  
#### Persistent cookies

Persistent cookies are stored on a users’ device in between browser sessions which allows the preferences or actions of the user across a site (or in some cases across different websites) to be remembered. Persistent cookies may be used for a variety of purposes including remembering users’ preferences and choices when using a site or to target advertising.

##### Strictly unnecessary cookies

Name| Typical Content| Usage| Expires  
---|---|---|---  
ICO_auth| Value 1| Controls your cookie preferences| 12 Months  
  
##### Performance Cookies

Name| Typical Content| Usage| Expires  
---|---|---|---  
ei_lastvisit| Number - Timestamp| Message Boards - time of last visit| 1 Year  
ei_lastactivity| Number - Time in seconds| Message Boards - time since last activity| 1 Year  
ei_userid| Number| Message Boards - your user id when chosen option to remember your login| 1 Year  
ei_password| Encrypted password| Message Boards - encrypted password when chosen option to remember your login| 1 Year  
vbulletin_collapse| String| Message Boards - Main Forum View Preferences| 1 Year  
  
##### Analytical Cookies

The Service Provider also use ‘analytical’ cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they’re using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example by making sure users are finding what they need easily.

Name| Typical Content| Usage| Expires  
---|---|---|---  
_utma| Random string| Session ID| 2 Years  
_utmb| Random string| Message Boards session ID| 30 Minutes  
_utmc| String| Message Boards - Last Viewed Threads| when you close your browser  
_utmz| Value 1| Message Boards - Thread preferences| 6 Months  
  
For more general information about cookies visit [All About cookies website](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

To find out how to turn cookies on and off in your browser visit following links:   

### Access To Personal Information The Service Provider May Hold About You

You can ask at any time whether The Service Provider is keeping any personal information about you and The Service Provider will endeavour to respond to you promptly and provide you with a readable copy of any personal information which we are keeping about you.

The Service Provider will also allow you to challenge any personal information that may be held about you and, where appropriate, you may have the information erased or amended. Proof of identity will be required before we can discuss with you any personal information that may be held about you and, there will be a £10 administration fee.

### Information Security

The Service Provider has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal information that The Service Provider has under control from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

### Advertising And Interactive Website Services

The Service Provider accept advertisements and interactive areas of The Website like the message boards enable website users to post personal information publicly and communicate with other website users. When your personal information is posted on The Website publicly or you communicate with other users of our websites, other users of our website may collect your personal information.

### Links

The Website contains links to third-party websites. If you access these links, you will leave The Website. The Service Provider does not control these other websites and their privacy practices may differ from this version.

### Privacy Support

If you have a privacy related enquiry, you can write to The Service Provider at ; 

You acknowledge that by continuing to browse/use this website and providing data to The Service Provider, you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

The Service Provider reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Statement at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. 

Last updated: 9th October 2014
